这三明治真是个彻底的失败品
This sandwich is an unmitigated disaster.
我点的是火鸡和烤牛肉
I asked for turkey and roast beef
全麦上放生菜和芝士
With lettuce and swiss on whole wheat.
那他们给你的什么?
What did they give you?
火鸡和烤牛肉
Turkey and roast beef
全麦上放的芝士和生菜
With swiss and lettuce on whole wheat.
东西确实一样  但是顺序不对啊
It's the right ingredients, but in the wrong order.
一个合格的三明治
In a proper sandwich,
它的芝士要紧贴着面包
The cheese is adjacent to the bread
这样会提供给生菜一个有水分的屏障
To create a moisture barrier against the lettuce.
他们可能带着这玩意过了一趟洗车房
They might as well have dragged this thing through a car wash.
不太可能吧
I don't believe it.
我知道  这是很基本的烹饪知识
I know. it's basic culinary science.
有人拍卖了一个原版电影里用过的时间机器道具
Some guy is auctioning off a miniature time machine prop
但竟然没人竞拍
From the original film, and no one is bidding on it.
电影"时间机器"里的时间机器?
A time machine from the movie the time machine?
不  是"苏菲的选择"里的时间机器
No. a time machine from sophie's choice.
厉害  苏菲在电影里是用过一个时间机器
Boy, sophie could have used a time machine in that movie.
你见过吗?  挺刚猛啊
Did you see it? it's rough.
酷毙了
Oh, that's cool.
只要800美金?
It's only $800?
没错  那是我出的价钱
Yeah. and that's my bid.
你出价800美元?
You bid $800?
我没多想一时定下的嘛
It was a spur-of-the-moment thing.
我想它怎么都会飙到上千的
I figured it would go for thousands,
我只是想参与一下而已
And I just wanted to be a part of it.
拍卖还剩30秒就结束了
There's only 30 seconds left in the auction.
你有800美金吗?
Do you have $800?
撼动不了这台小型时间机器
Not to blow on a miniature time machine.
别担心  一般大家都是
Well, don't worry. the way these things work
等到最后一秒钟
Is people wait until the last second to bid,
然后突然杀进来把它拍走  这就叫淘宝
And then they swoop in and get it. it's called sniping.
15秒
15 seconds.
快点啊  淘宝人
Come on, snipers.
10  9  8...
Ten, nine, eight...
你的淘宝人呢?
Where are your snipers?
5  淘啊
Five... snipe.
4  淘啊
Four... snipe.
3  淘啊
Three... snipe!
2  淘啊
Two... snipe!
One...
祝贺你
Congratulations!
你光荣地成为这台小型时间机器的主人了
You are the proud owner of a miniature time machine!
你个幸运的家伙
You lucky duck.
我想不通怎么没人竞拍了
I wonder why no one else bid.
这是部经典高科技电影里很有纪念意义的东西啊
This is a classic piece of sci-fi movie memorabilia.
我知道  可我仍然没钱买它
Yeah, I know! I still can't afford it.
要不我们一起凑钱吧?
Why don't we share it?
我们每人出200
We'll each put in 200 bucks, and we'll
然后我们轮流把它放家里
Take turns having it in our house.
一个时间共享的时间机器
A time-share time machine.
我同意  谢尔顿?
I'm in. sheldon?
还用你问吗?
Need you ask?
可我还是不明白怎么就没人出价
I still don't understand why no one else bid.
我明白为什么没人出价了
I understand why no one else bid.
《生活大爆炸》
第一季  第14集
The.Nerdvana.Annihilation
那单子上确实有写是小型的吗?
Did the listing actually say "miniature"?
我也在想
I just assumed.
谁会800块就卖一个完整尺寸的时间机器啊?
Who sells a full-size time machine for $800?
某人肯定处于两块韦恩集合图的交集
In a venn diagram, that would be an individual located
一张集合图写着"不再需要时间机器"
Within the intersection of the sets "no longer want my time machine"
另一张写着"急需800块"
And "need $800."
这个价钱的确非常低了
It's actually a tremendous bargain.
就算加上运费
Even with shipping, it works out
算下来平均每磅不到4美金呢
To less than four dollars a pound.
调味酱稣虾是12块5
Cocktail shrimp are $12.50.
我们怎么把这玩意弄上楼?
How are we going to get it upstairs?
如果把这个盘子取下来
If we take the dish off,
应该能放进电梯里
It might fit in the elevator.
对  可是电梯都坏了2年了
Yes, but the elevator has been broken for two years.
我曾经想问过你
I've been meaning to ask you.
你说我们是不是该打个电话呢
Do you think we should make a call about that?
没必要
Not necessary.
我是工程学硕士
I have a master's in engineering.
我闭眼都能远程修复卫星
I remotely repair satellites on a regular basis.
我还能检修航天飞机载弹头
I troubleshoot space shuttle payloads.
当火星探测器开始向左行驶时
When the mars rover started pulling to the left, I performed
我在6200万英里以外进行用户接口联合
A front-end alignment from 62 million miles away.
不  这宝贝已经坏了
No. that baby's broken.
加油啊  伙计们  用力推!
Come on, guys! push!
如果我再用力
If I push any harder,
就快把结肠给"分娩"出来了
I'm going to give birth to my colon.
我手指都快没知觉了  快点!
I can't feel my fingers. hurry up!
不管多快
It's the same amount of work
工作量都是一样的
No matter how fast you go.
基本的物理原理
Basic physics.
-谢尔顿?  -干嘛?
Sheldon? yeah?
如果我的手指以后还能用
If my fingers ever work again,
我想我的中指以后有活干了
I've got a job for the middle one.
好  各位
Oh. hey, guys.
你好  佩妮
Oh. hi, penny.
休息一会吧
Take a break, guys.
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
我们在...搬点东西上来
We're just, you know, moving something upstairs.
什么东西
What is it?
就是个...时间机器
Just... you know. time machine.
好的  不错  但我要赶去工作了  所以...
Yeah. okay. neat. but I really got to get to work.
-再给我们几分钟  -我等不了几分钟
Just give us a few minutes. I don't have a few minutes.
我已经晚了
I'm running really late.
我有个简单的办法
Then, I have a simple solution.
去到楼顶  跳到另一栋楼顶上
Go up to the roof. hop over to the next building.
中间离得不远
There's a small gap--
如果你容易晕就别往下看
Don't look down if you're subject to vertigo--
然后走他们的楼梯井
And use their stairwell.
你逗我玩呢  是吧?
You're joking, right?
跟头晕有关的东西我从不开玩笑
Oh, I never joke when it comes to vertigo.
该死  好吧  我去房顶看看
Damn. okay, I'll just take the roof.
如果你能等我们把时间机器都弄好了
Hey, if you wait for us to set up the time machine,
我可以把你送回到昨天上班时
I can drop you off at work yesterday.
时光旅行  开个玩笑...别介意
Time travel joke. it's not... never mind.
从它的用途来看  我觉得还是挺好笑的
For what it's worth, I thought it was humorous.
还是接着搬吧
Let's just do this.
兄弟们准备好推了没?
You guys ready to push?
马上
In a minute.
霍华德到外面去吐了
Howard stepped outside to throw up.
我不懂你到底在担心什么
I don't know what you were worried about.
我觉得他放在房间里肯定能行
I think it really works in the room.
是啊
Yeah.
这绝对是我拥有过的
It is by far the coolest thing
最酷的东西
I have ever owned.
那个载着演员罗德・泰勒
The exact time machine that carried actor rod taylor
从维多利亚时代的英格兰
From victorian england
到临近未来世界末日的时间机器
Into the post-apocalyptic future,
那个社会分裂成两个派系
Where society had splintered into the two factions
居住在地下的"莫洛克"
The subterranean morlocks, who survived by feasting
他们靠吃住在地表的"埃洛依"维生
On the flesh of the gentle surface-dwelling eloi.
真是性感的万人迷啊
Talk about your chick magnets.
是  没错
Oh, yeah.
那个住我旁隔壁的家伙总是
The guy who lives next to me is always like,
"我的阳台上有个水流按摩浴缸
"i have a jacuzzi on my balcony.
我的阳台上有个水流按摩浴缸"
I have a jacuzzi on my balcony."
可等着看我告诉他
But wait until I tell him,
"我的阳台上有一台时间机器
"i've got a time machine on my balcony.
把泳裤裹裹紧吧  按摩浴缸"
Stuff that in your speedo, jacuzzi bob."
先生们  我知道我们说好是轮流拥有它
Gentlemen, I know we said we'd take turns,
但我想你们会认同说
But I think you'll agree
实际上就意味着它是留在这儿的
That practicality dictates it remain here.
你不能就这么独吞了
You can't just keep it here.
假如我碰到个小妞然后跟她说
What if I meet a girl and say,
"你想上去看看我的时间机器吗
"you want to come up and see my time machine?
它在我朋友家里"
It's at my friends' house."
多丢人啊!
How lame is that?
-他说的对  -好吧
He's got a point. all right,
我觉得我们该订些基本原则
I think we're going to need some ground rules; in addition
除了"进时间机器禁止穿鞋"
To the expected "no shoes in the time machine,"
以及"时间机器内禁止饮食"
And "no eating in the time machine,"
我还建议"进时间机器
I propose we add "pants must be worn
必须要穿裤子'
At all times in the time machine."
赞成!
Seconded.
我还准备在里面放条毛巾呢
I was going to put down a towel.
我还是希望它能放在我的阳台上
I still want it on my balcony.
我说我们就两月轮一次(或一月轮两次)吧
I say we move it on a bi-monthly basis.
是啊  听上去挺公平
Yeah, that sounds fair.
等等  两月轮一次很模棱两可啊
Hold on, bi-monthly is an ambiguous term.
意思是每两月搬一次还是每个月搬两次?
Do you mean move it every other month or twice a month?
-一月两次  -那就不行
Twice a month. then no.
那好  两月一次
Okay, every other month.
还是不行
No.
谢尔顿  你不能这么自私!
Sheldon, you can't be selfish.
我们都付了钱  所以它是大家的
We all paid for it, so it belongs to all of us.
现在快让开  别挡着我进我的时间机器
Now get out of the way so I can sit in my time machine.
好的  我设置时间到1876年3月10日
Okay, I am setting the dials for march 10, 1876.
好主意  亚历山大・格雷厄姆・贝尔
Good choice, alexander graham bell
发明了电话并打给了沃森博士
Invents the telephone and calls out for dr. watson.
等等  我也想看看这个场面
Wait a minute. I'd want to see that, too.
轮到你的时候  随你想干嘛
So when it's your turn, you can.
不过如果我们都去同一个时间点
But if we all go back to the same point in time,
贝尔的实验室就太挤了
Bell's lab is going to get very crowded.
他就会知道有大事发生了
He'll know something's up.
而且时间机器不会进行空间上的位移
Also since the time machine doesn't move in space,
所以你会"降临"在1876年的帕萨迪纳
You'll end up in 1876 pasadena.
即使你降临在了波士顿  你又能干嘛呢
And even if you can make it to boston, what are you going to do?
敲贝尔的门跟贝尔夫人说
Knock on the door and say to mrs. bell,
"嘿  贝尔夫人  我是你老公的疯狂粉丝
"hey, mrs. bell. big fan of your husband.
我能进来参观他发明电话吗?"
Can I come in and watch him invent the telephone?"
贝尔夫人是个聋子
Mrs. bell was deaf.
她甚至不会听到你敲门
She's not even going to hear you knock.
我有个办法
I have a solution.
首先去到未来弄一个隐身装置
First, go into the future and obtain a cloaking device.
多远的未来?
Ooh, how far into the future?
如果我没记错的话
If I remember correctly,
柯克舰长会在星际纪年5027.3
Captain kirk will steal a cloaking device
从罗姆兰偷走一个隐身装置(出自"星际迷航"系列)
From the romulans on stardate 5027.3,
之后被'先锋联盟舰队'于2328年1月10日所截获
Which would be january 10, 2328 by pre-federation reckoning.
好吧  那我把时间设到2328年1月10日
Okay, I am setting the dials for january 10, 2328.
向未来  出发
Here we go into the future.
真有意思
That was fun.
轮到我了
My turn!
首先
Okay, first of all,
那段你声称仅三英尺宽的距离
What you call a gap was nearly three feet wide.
-让我滑倒摔伤了我的膝盖  -你还好吧?
I slipped and skinned my knee. are you okay?
其次  那扇通往旁边那幢楼的
Second of all, the door to the stairwell
楼梯井门是锁着的
Of the other building was locked,
所以我不得不从防火梯下楼
So I had to go down the fire escape,
可那只是到三楼的
Which ends on the third floor,
逼我只能从一个"可爱"的亚美尼亚家庭
Forcing me to crawl through the window
的窗户爬了进去
Of a lovely armenian family
他们还强留了我吃午饭
Who insisted I stay for lunch.
听起来还不坏嘛
That doesn't sound too bad.
那是整整八斤羔羊肉
It was eight courses of lamb,
他们还试图撮合我和他们的儿子
And they tried to fix me up with their son.
-对不起  -还没完呢
I'm sorry. not done.
等我终于好不容易
By the time I finally
赶到那里上班  他们已经把我的班给换了
Got to work, they'd given my shift away.
是啊  没错
Yeah, that's right.
我损失了一整天的工资  就因为这个
I lost an entire day's pay thanks to this.
-这个...  -时间机器
This... time machine.
灯会一闪一闪  托盘还会转  你想不想试试?
The lights flash and the dish spins. you want to try it?
才不!
No!
我才不想试试!
I don't want to try it!
天哪  你们都已经是成年人了!
My god, you are grown men!
你们怎么能浪费生命
How can you waste your lives with these
整天弄这些蠢玩具和傻戏服
Stupid toys and costumes
还有漫画书还有...那个?!
And comic books and... and now that?!
-那个...  -再次提醒  时间机器
That... again. time machine.
拜托  那才不是什么时间机器
Oh, please, it's not a time machine.
这顶多就是看上去像艾尔顿・约翰
If anything, it looks like something
驶过大沼泽地的代步工具
Elton john would drive through the everglades.
这个只能在时间上移动
It only moves in time.
这个在沼泽地里会比无用更无用
It would be worse than useless in a swamp.
可悲!  你们这群人!
Pathetic! all of you!
可悲到了极点!
Completely pathetic!
该我了
My turn.
莱纳德  现在可是凌晨2点
Leonard, it's 2:00 in the morning.
怎么了
So?
该我了
So it's my turn.
你为什么把时间设在前天?
Why did you set it for the day before yesterday?
因为我想回到那天
Because I want to go back and keep myself
阻止自己买时间机器
From getting a time machine.
这做不到  如果你想在过去
You can't. if you were to prevent yourself
阻止自己买时间机器
From buying it in the past,
你就不可能现在拥有一台时间机器
You would not have it available in the present
然后利用它回到过去
To travel back and stop yourself
阻止自己买它  所以你仍然会拥有它
From buying it. ergo, you would still have it.
这是典型的时间旅行低级错误
This is a classic rookie time-travel mistake.
我可以回到过去让你闭嘴吗?
Can I go back and prevent you from explaining that to me?
同样的低级错误
Same paradox.
如果你想回到过去
If you were to travel back in time
比如说  把我打晕
And, say, knock me unconscious,
那就不会有现在的对话
You would not then have the conversation
来把你激怒  让你想回到过去
That irritated you, motivating you
并且把我打晕
To go back and knock me unconscious.
如果我现在想把你打晕呢?
What if I knocked you unconscious right now?
那也改变不了过去
It won't change the past.
不过会让我现在好受很多
But it'd make the present so much nicer.
你有什么事心烦吗
Are you upset about something?
你从哪看出来的
What was your first clue?
有很多地方
Well, it was a number of things.
首先  你睡得很晚
First, the late hour.
其次  你的言行似乎没有活力
Then your demeanor seems very low-energy,
再加上你很易怒
Plus your irritability.
是的  我很心烦!
Yes, I'm upset!
我一般可不大了解这些的
I don't usually pick up on those things.
我不赖啊
Good for me.
是啊  你不赖
Yeah, good for you.
等等
Oh, wait.
你想聊聊为什么事心烦吗?
Did you want to talk about what's bothering you?
不知道  可以吧
I don't know. maybe.
哇  我今晚真是太强了
Wow. I'm on fire tonight.
...是这样
Uh... here's the thing.
像佩妮这样的女孩是不会和玩时间机器的人在一起的
Girls like penny never end up with guys who own time machines.
我不同意
I disagree.
你追求佩妮失败的经历
Your inability to successfully woo penny
是要远远早于得到时间机器的日期的
Long predates your acquisition of the time machine.
这个失败是显而易见的
That failure clearly stands on its own.
多谢指出
Thanks for pointing it out.
此外  你的前提是有瑕疵的
In addition, your premise is flawed.
在原版电影中  罗德・泰勒就是用时间机器
In the original film, rod taylor got yvette mimieux
得到了伊薇特・米米亚克斯(电影女主角)
With that very time machine.
回到未来  马帝・麦克佛莱得到了机会
In back to the future, marty mcfly got the opportunity
和他魅力十足的年轻妈妈鬼混
To hook up with his extremely attractive young mother.
那些都是电影
Those are movies.
当然都是电影
Of course they're movies.
你难道指望我举出个现实版
Were you expecting me to come up with an example
时间机器的例子吗?
Involving a real-life time machine?
荒谬
That's absurd.
加油啊  伙计们  用力推!
Come on, guys, push!
如果我再用力
If I push any harder,
就快把结肠给"分娩"出来了
I'm going to give birth to my colon.
好  各位
Oh, hey, guys.
你好  佩妮
Oh. hi, penny.
休息一会吧
Take a break, guys!
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
你知道  就是搬搬时间机器
Oh, you know, just moving a time machine.
好的  不错  但我要赶去工作了  所以...
Yeah. okay, neat, but I really gotta get to work, so...
没问题
No problem.
坚持一下
Hang on.
但是...你的时间机器怎么办
But... what about your time machine?
有些事情比玩具更重要
Some things are more important than toys.
我好害怕
I'm scared.
不要害怕  宝贝  有我在
Don't worry, baby. I've got you.
哦  莱纳德
Oh, leonard.
仍旧该我了
It's still my turn.
你干什么
What are you doing?
把我收集的所有东西打包
I'm packing up all my collectibles
然后带下去卖给漫画书店
And taking them down to the comic book store to sell.
真的有必要吗
Was that really necessary?
如果需要钱  你随时可以卖血啊
If you need money, you can always sell blood.
还有精液
And semen.
这和钱无关
This is not about money.
我们带了吃的
We brought food!
熏鲑鱼和硬面包圈  时间旅人的早餐
Lox and bagels, the breakfast of time-travelers.
棒极了
Terrific.
有人想要买我时间机器里的股份吗
Does anyone want to buy my share of the time machine?
怎么
Why?
我不想再要了
I don't want it anymore.
为什么
Why?
...私人原因
Just... personal reasons.
我蜘蛛侠一般的嗅觉告诉我
My spidey sense tells me
这和佩妮有关
This has something to do with penny.
听着
Look,
-你们到底想不想要买股份?  -我给你
Do you want to buy me out or not? I'll give you
100美元  这样我就是半个拥有者了
A hundred dollars, which will make me half-owner
然后我们把它放到我的阳台上去
And we'll put it on my balcony.
去你的阳台
Screw his balcony.
我给你120美元  我要放到我的车库
I'll give you $120 and we'll put it in my garage.
我的股份当时是200美金
I paid $200 for my share.
小子  大家都知道
Dude, everybody knows
时间机器会因为转让
A time machine loses half its value
而贬低一半的价值
The minute you drive it off the lot.
我付200
I'll go for $200.
让时间机器就呆在原地
That time machine stays right where it is.
我付300
$300 and I'll throw in
我要打造最初的1973年的星战飞船
My original 1979 mattel millennium falcon
并使之兼具真正的光速和声效
With real light speed sound effects.
不  不再要玩具和动作模型了
No. no more toys or action figures
也不要道具  复制品  戏服还有机器人
Or props or replicas or costumes or robots
也不要达斯・维德的变声工具了
Or darth vader voice changers.
我不想再要所有这些了
I'm getting rid of all of it.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
看看你收集的这些吧
Look what you've created here.
这就像是封闭的电脑狂人
It's like nerdvana.
更重要的是
More importantly,
你有达斯・维德的变声工具?
You have a darth vader voice changer?
不会再有了
Not for long.
我有权要求那"Golden Age Flash"(一部漫画)
Oh, I call dibs on the golden age flash.
等等  我要靠它来
Hang on. I need that
集全"正义联盟"(一部漫画)
To complete my justice society of america collection.
太遗憾了  我有权要求了
Too bad. I called dibs.
-你不能这么有权要求的  -我既可以也叫了
You can't just call dibs. I can and I did.
去维基百科查查"有权要求"吧
Look up "dibs" in wikipedia.
在竞价战中是没有有权要求的
Dibs doesn't apply in a bidding war.
这不是竞价战
It's not a bidding war.
我全部要卖给楼下漫画书店的拉里
I'm selling it all to larry down at the comic book store.
为什么是拉里  拉力有权要求了?
Why larry? did larry call dibs?
你能不能别提有权要求了?!
Will you forget dibs?!
就这整套东西
He offered me a fair price
他提了个合理的价钱
For the whole collection.
多少?  我给同样价钱
What's the number? I'll match it.
我给同样价钱再加一千卢比
I'll match it plus a thousand rupees.
-汇率是多少  -不关你事
What's the exchange rate? none of your business.
成还不成?
Take it or leave it?
妈妈  我的成年礼债券在吗
Mom? my bar mitzvah bonds.
我有多少?
How much do I got?
谢谢
Thanks.
我可以出价2600美金加上以色列的两颗树
I can go $2,600 and two trees in israel.
算了  伙计们
Forget it, guys.
如果我卖给了你们其中一个
If I sell to one of you,
另外两个会对我大光其火的
The other two are going to be really mad at me.
管他呢
Who cares?
只要你卖给我
As long as you pick me!
好了  莱纳德  把盒子放下
Okay, leonard, put down the box.
-我们谈谈  -抱歉  拉杰
Let's talk. sorry, raj.
我已经决定了
My mind is made up.
不!
No!
我一定得阻止你
I can't let you do this.
谢尔顿  你让开
Sheldon, get out of my way.
没人可以过去!
None shall pass!
好吧
Okay.
我不想这样的
I did not want to do this, but
可我手上拿的是完好无损的
I have here the rare mint condition production error
星舰迷航里下一代不带视觉辅助器的
Star Trek the next generation geordi la forge
乔迪拉弗吉的珍贵原版纪念品
Without his visor in the original packaging.
如果你们继续挡我的路
If you do not get out of my way,
我就把它拆封了
I will open it.
好  伙计  冷静
Okay, man. be cool.
我们是自己人
We're all friends here.
你们在搞什么
What the hell's going on?
你个伪善者!
You hypocrite!
什么?
What?
"长大了不能玩玩具"小姐
Little miss "grown-ups don't play with toys."
如果我现在进你那间屋子
If I were to go into that apartment right now,
我会找不到豆豆娃?
Would I not find beanie babies?
难道你不收集
Are you not an accumulator
小熊公仔和维尼?
Of care bears and my little ponies?
看看在你热裤上嬉戏的日本小猫又是什么
And who is that japanese feline I see frolicking on your shorts?
你好  Hello Kitty!
Hello, hello kitty!
好
Okay.
好  听着  如果是因为昨天的事  莱纳德
Okay, look, if this is about yesterday, leonard,
我为我昨天的话感到抱歉
I am really sorry about what I said.
我只是有点心烦而已
I was just upset.
不  还是很中听的
No, I needed to hear it.
不  不是的  真的  你是个很好的人
No, you didn't. look, you are a great guy
而这是你喜欢的东西  这才是你的本色
And it is the things you love that make you who you are.
我猜这就是"我的大波"
I guess that makes me "large breasts."
但是
Still,
我还是觉得是时候跟这些东西说再见了
I think it's time for me to get rid of this stuff
然后  开始新的生活
And, you know, move on with my life.
真的?
Really?
是的
Yeah.
不错
Well, good for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
你想不想...
Hey, do you want to...
也许过一会...
I don't know, later...
不好意思
Excuse me.
-佩妮  -麦克
Hey, penny. hi, mike.
-可以走了吗  -可以  等我换换衣服
You ready to go? oh, yeah. I just have to change.
我来帮你一把
I'll give you a hand.
别闹了
Oh, stop it!
再见
Bye, guys.
轮到我坐时间机器了
My turn on the time machine.
成了
It worked.
真的成了
It really worked.
他们说我疯了  但真的成了!
They said I was mad, but it worked!
不
Oh, no!
不要莫洛克!
Not morlocks!
不要吃人肉的莫洛克!
Not flesh-eating morlocks!
救命!
Help!
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我们得远离这台时间机器
We have to get rid of the time machine.
放在客厅里是有点太大了  是不是?
It is a little big for the living room, isn't it?
是  是这样
Yeah, that's the problem.
太大了
It's too big.
很高兴你也这么觉得  我叫了人来帮忙搬走
Glad you agree. I'm to help us move it.
进来吧  伙计们
Come on in, fellas.
不
Oh, no.
莫洛克!
Morlocks!
吃他  吃他
Eat him. eat him.